Guide to the Terry Allen Winograd Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Subject Files, individual
  - Schon, Donald A. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Selker, Ted (1 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Selker, Ted (2 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Shanon, Benny (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Shaw, David E. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Shneiderman, Ben (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Simon, Herb A. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Brian (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Sproull, Lee (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Suchman, Lucy (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Supes, Patrick (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - "T" Students (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Taylor, Charles (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Turkle, Sherry (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Tversky, Amos (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - "V" Students (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Varela, Francisco (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Verplank, Bill (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Von Foerster, Heinz (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - "W" Students (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Weizenbaum, Joseph (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Whiteside, John (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - "Y" Students (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - DL Proposal (1 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - DL Proposal (2 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Computer files
  - Teaching (Squirrel Pres), Undated; 0 (Box 37)
  - Better Game Characters by Design, 2006; 0 (Box 37)
  - Camille Utterback, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - CHI, 2005-2009; 5 optical disc(s) (DVD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Conference on Computer Supported Cooperative Work, 2006 Nov 4-8; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - UbiComp Video Proceedings, 2003 Oct. 12-15; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Using Video to Support Interactive Design, Undated; 2 optical disc(s) (DVD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems, 2003 Apr 5-10; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - 5th Graders in the iRoom, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 37)
  - Apple Color Graphics Sampler, 1991; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Mark Weiser, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 37)
  - Favorite Greek Myths, 1994; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - CS447B, 1999; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 37)
  - The University Workshop Sketchbook, 1995; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - The Tortoise and the Hare, 1993; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - From Alice to Ocean, 1992; 2 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - The Beatles in a Hard Day's Night, 1993; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Interface 93 Design Project, 1994; 2 optical disc(s) (CR-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Design95 Project Files, 1995; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Making it Macintosh, 1993; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Myst User's Manual, 1993; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Planetary Taxi, 1993; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Sounds Toys, Undated; 1 case(s) (Box 37)
  - CS 147 Dissect-A-Frog, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 37)
  - Untitled, Undated; 1 audio cassette (micro-cassette) (Box 37)
  - CHI, 2001-2004; 4 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Computer Graphics Conference Proceedings, 1999; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Design Computing and Cognition, 2008; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - The Face of Design, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - DUX Designing for User Experiences, 2003; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - VIS 2000 IEEE Visualization, 2000 Oct 8-13; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - International Symposium on Creative Digital media, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 37)
  - New Paradigms For Using Computer, 1999; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - PUI 2001, 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - SI99raph Conference Abstracts and Applications, 1999; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - SI99 Electronic Art and Animation Catalog, 1999; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - SIGGRAPH 99 Course Notes, 1999; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - UbiComp Active Campus & Place Lab Demos, 2003; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - 5th International World-Wide Web Conference, 1996, May 6-10; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - 6th International World-Wide Web Conference, 1997 Apr 7-11; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - 7th International World-Wide Eb Conference, 1998 Apr 14-18; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Inside Magic, 1995; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Journey to the Edge, 1997; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - The Journeyman Project, 1992; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Logical Journey of the Zoombinis, 1996; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Awesome Animated Monster Maker, 1995; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Monty Python's Complete Waste of Time, 1994; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Corbis Bettmann, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - The Peter B. Lewis Building Catalyst, 2000; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Designing Business, 1996; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Digital Design 2000+, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - The Disappearing Computer, 2003; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Paul Cezanne Portrait of My World, 1996; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Refresh The Art of the Screensaver, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - W's Pay Per Rom, 1997; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Kai's Power Goo, Undated; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Microsoft BOB, 1994; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Greetings Workshop, 1996-1997; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Stagecast Creator, 1998-1999; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Vellum 3D, 1997; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-ROM) (Box 37)
  - Agile Aging Workshop
  - Business_Processes
  - CS147
  - Documents
  - Empathy Activity
  - HCI_20th
  - I-Work_2001
  - MMM
  - Nygaard, Kristen
  - IRoom_18min, 2000; 1 computer file(s) (MOV)
  - SDLIPVideoCD-ROM, 1 computer file(s) (MOV)